I find it genuinely odd that people be talking about saving the United States because I don't
know what you're saving. You don't know what you're saving. And to be quite honest, there was
no way that this place was going to actually last. It's been run by mediocre white men for
the majority of its existence. I mean, it's been supported by everybody else, but that's
been running the show. And when you really start just looking into the way these presidencies
and the way Congress be operating, you're like, hold up. They've been, and the Supreme
Court, they've been running this thing into the grisound from day one. From day one. It
was never going to last. So start thinking of something better because this thing about
to wrap up in my lifetime. Remember I said it. And for the record, it's happened to many
other places. We were never impervious to this conclusion. Support a real one.